now an IntelliJ IDEA your project is
现在您的项目是IntelliJ IDEA
organized into one or more modules and
组织成一个或多个模块
these modules represent a collection of
这些模块代表了
sources and other resources that the IDE
IDE的资源和其他资源
will use in order to build your project
将用于构建您的项目
so each of these modules can have one or
因此这些模块中的每个模块都可以具有一个或
more facets associated with them and
与他们相关的更多方面
these facets are a technology or a
这些方面是技术还是
framework that IntelliJ IDEA will use to
IntelliJ IDEA将用于的框架
sort of help understand how your project
有助于您了解项目的方式
and each module is organized and so say
每个模块都是有组织的
it's a web facet so then it will have
这是一个网络方面，因此它将具有
some configuration files associated with
一些与之相关的配置文件
it some XML files and some deployment
一些XML文件和一些部署
descriptors that will tell intelligent
描述符将告诉智能
idea where to deploy your web app you
知道将Web应用程序部署到哪里
can manage all of these facets inside
可以管理内部所有这些方面
your project under the project structure
项目结构下的项目
dialog here under project settings
在项目设置下的对话框
you'll select facets you can see that
您将选择构面，您会看到
there are three types of facets
有三种类型的构面
associated with this project that I'm
我与此项目相关联
working with right now if you add a new
如果您添加新的，现在就可以使用
facet you can optionally enable
您可以选择启用方面
framework detection where IntelliJ IDEA
IntelliJ IDEA的框架检测
will detect any modules that are added
将检测添加的任何模块
to your project based on their unique
根据您的项目的独特性
file and directory structure so if I'd
文件和目录结构，如果我愿意
like to add a new facet in my project
想在我的项目中添加一个新的方面
and I can add say a GWT facet I can
我可以说一个GWT构面
choose any one of these modules to add
选择以下任一模块添加
it into so let's say I'd like to add it
它添加到，所以说我想添加它
into this one I'll click OK and since we
进入这一行，我将单击“确定”，因为我们
already have a web facet associated with
已经具有与
this module IntelliJ IDEA will allow us
此模块IntelliJ IDEA将允许我们
to select that facet as a target and
选择该方面作为目标并
then we can give it a path the GWT
那么我们可以给它一个GWT的路径
installation directory and so forth so
安装目录等等
not only will you'll be able to add and
您不仅可以添加和
remove these facets to your modules but
删除这些方面到您的模块，但
IntelliJ IDEA will allow you to use one
IntelliJ IDEA将允许您使用一个
or more facets together and it will give
或更多的方面在一起，它将给
you the tools to make them work side by
您使它们并行工作的工具
side you can find support for many types
方面，您可以找到许多类型的支持
of facets under the ad facet menu here
广告方面菜单下的方面
everything from languages to frameworks
从语言到框架的一切
to tools that you can use to build your
可以用来构建自己的工具
project and all of these are available
项目，所有这些都可用
when you create a new project as well so
在创建新项目时也是如此
if you open up the new project dialog
如果您打开新项目对话框
when you create the project you can
当您创建项目时，您可以
select additional libraries and
选择其他库并
frameworks to use with inside your
在您的内部使用的框架
project these will be automatically set
项目这些将自动设置
up so that when you create your project
以便在创建项目时
you'll have a template right there
您将在那里有一个模板
waiting for you thanks for watching
等着你谢谢收看